100percentdesign.co.uk 2018-03-12

# Privacy Policy - 100% Design 2017 - The UK's biggest trade event for architects and designers

This site is owned and operated by Media 10 Limited. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Media 10, we want to make your experience online satisfying and saf

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**INFORMATION MEDIA 10 LIMITED GATHERS AND TRACKS**

Media 10 Ltd gathers two types of information about users:

a) Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls, surveys and competitions.

b) Information Media 10 Ltd gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers'/users needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because Media 10 Ltd derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential. Under no circumstances does Media 10 divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

**Media 10 Ltd Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:**

Optional Voluntary Information

We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

1\. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)

We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Media 10 Ltd gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management.

2\. Message boards/forums policy

Users of any website's Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they need not register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.

3\. "E-mail this to a friend" policy

Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

4\. Your participation on our Site may mean that we occasionally contact you with the opportunity to enter competitions. Entry to competitions is voluntary, and you are under no obligation to take up an invitation from us to enter. Should you choose to enter a competition, we will treat the information you provide with the same high standard of care as all other customer information, and use the information provided strictly within the entry terms of the competition and this Privacy Statement.

5\. Polling

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Media 10 Ltd may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

6\. Surveys

Media 10 Ltd may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

**Children**

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

**Usage tracking**

Media 10 Ltd tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Media 10 Ltd does break down overall usage statistics according to a users domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

Media 10 Ltd sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that user's enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

**Cookies**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can not read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Media 10 Ltd uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling, surveys and competitions.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

Media 10 Ltd uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites or products, whether to provide interactive or personalised elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, competitions, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Media 10 Ltd never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas, we do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we do not track which terms a particular user enters.

Media 10 creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we do not track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**SHARING OF THE INFORMATION**

Media 10 Ltd uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**PHOTOGRAPHY AND FILMING**

As a visitor I agree to my image or likeness of, being used in the photographing, recording and filming of on-site activities. This may come in the form of organiser promotional material, sponsor, exhibitor and media partner coverage. I understand that this media may be shared post-show in print, online and on broadcast television.

**SECURITY**

Media 10 Ltd operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

**OPT-IN / OUT POLICY**

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

Opting to register to receive our electronic newsletters.

Opting to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.

Ability to opt-out of email news letters.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Media 10. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Data Protection Registration Number: Z1245054

**WEBSITE**

[ASP](http://www.asp.com/ "http://www.asp.com") provide and host this website for Media 10. [ASP](http://www.asp.com/ "http://www.asp.com") is registered with the UK Data Commissioner as Data Controllers and hold all the data within the UK.

**Contact Details**

Media 10 Limited  
Crown House  
151 High Road  
Loughton  
IG10 4LF  
Tel: 020 3225 5200

Email: [privacy@media-ten.com](mailto:privacy@media-ten.com?Subject=100%25%20Design%20Enquiry "privacy@media-ten.com")
